indiafirstlife.com 2019-03-17

# Privacy Policy | IndiaFirst Life Insurance

The Privacy policy governs the use of this website of IndiaFirst Life Insurance Company Limited (“IndiaFirst”) (www.indiafirstlife.com  ).

Please read the terms of use carefully. By accessing or using this website and its pages (collectively, this "Website"), you agree to be bound by the terms of use and accept them in full. IndiaFirst may change the terms of use from time to time and changes will be posted on this Website. By continuing to access and use this site after any such changes are posted, you will be deemed to have accepted such changes. Not all consumers will be eligible for the products and services described on the Website, and we reserve the right to determine your eligibility for any product or service.

**How do we collect your information and what does it comprise?**

We collect information from you when you register on our Website, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form.

We may also collect information regarding the domain and host from which you access the internet, the internet protocol address of the computer or internet service provider you are using, anonymous statistical data, and any and all details that may be necessary from you.

If you are visiting our Website from outside India, your visit will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international borders, which you consent, and are deemed to consent to, by using our Website.

All information or documentation given by you will be deemed to be and shall be treated by IndiaFirst Life as true, accurate and complete. If you choose to visit the Website anonymously, all functions on our Website may not be available to you.

**How do we use your information?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalise your experience: your information helps us respond better to your individual needs.

To improve the Website: we continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

To improve customer service: your information helps us to effectively respond to your customer service requests, and support needs, and connect with you as required.

To process transactions: your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

To send periodic emails: (a) The email address you give us to process an order will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to it.  
(b) If you decide to join our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

If you’d like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please refer to the detailed instructions for unsubscribing that appear at the bottom of our emails.

**How do we protect your information?**

When you place an order or access your personal information on our Website, we implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers’ database only to be accessible by those authorised with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, we do. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you consent) that enables the sites or service providers’ systems to recognise your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about the site and its interactions so that we can offer better experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting our customer service through the contact page on our Website.

No Personal Information is gathered or stored in the cookies placed by our Website and, as a result, none can be passed on to any third parties.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

 **

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

By agreeing to the Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy, you authorise us to share your information with a third party, who we may process the information collected to serve you better. We will not disclose your information to outside parties unless such action is necessary to:

  * Protect our rights, interests, reputation or property; or
  * Comply with the applicable law; or
  * If such information is required under any judicial or arbitral pronouncement or order; or
  * Enforce the Terms and Conditions of our products or services or the Terms and Conditions.

We will take all appropriate and reasonable measures to protect your personally identifiable information, and you expressly acknowledge and agree that any information that is transmitted to us via our Website may not be secure from third-party interference and we will not be liable or deemed to be liable for any such interference.

You may, at any time, inform us, not to share your information with the third party by intimating us via email. We may share non-personally identifiable visitor information with other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses at our discretion.

**

In addition to the circumstances described above, IndiaFirst may disclose the member information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other Government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect our rights or properties, or any, or all of our affiliates, associates, employees, directors or officers, or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. In addition, if IndiaFirst or substantially all of its assets are acquired, the Personal Information provided by the User will most likely also be transferred in connection with such acquisition.

****
